Oh. Ls it? Listen.
- What, you don't like wind chimes?
- No, I hate them, but it gets worse.
(Sheldon:)- There it is.
- The bird?
(Sheldon:)Yeah, it's completely out of tune
with the wind chimes.
- So?
- You don't get it, do you?
(Sheldon:)That's a mockingbird.
Mockingbirds can change their song...
(Sheldon:)...which means
he's out of tune on purpose.
(Sheldon:)He's mocking me.
(Sheldon:)Oh, dear, there it is again.
Do you feel it?
(Howard:)The growing realization
that you are one wacky bastard? Yep.
(Sheldon:)No. The vibration.
(Sheldon:)We are directly
underneath the geology lab...
(Sheldon:)...and they're running
their sieve shakers again.
(Sheldon:)Hey, gravel monkeys,
you need to shake rocks?
(Sheldon:)Try jiggling your heads around!
- Sheldon, relax.
- How can I relax?
(Sheldon:)My nervous system is being
stretched out like the strings of a harp...
(Sheldon:)...and plucked by holes
and birds and wind...
(Sheldon:)...and the low-hanging scrotum of the
difficuIt-to-evict Professor Rothman.